"Come unto Me all ye that labour."
Here are Your children; they have come to You, Lord.
Every affliction in their blood, disease in their blood -
wherever it is located, I release them in the name of Jesus!
You disease - out, in the name of Jesus!
I say out, in the name of Jesus!
Command them out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever it is - in your faculties - distance is not a barrier.
I say to that your affliction, "Leave my people!".
I say to that disease, "Leave my people".
I say to that sickness, "Leave my people!"
"Leave my people!"
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, begin to walk out of disease.
I feel the touch of Jesus.
Walk out of disease!
I can see you being delivered.
I can see you being healed.
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, if it is true for your life that you are healed, you are delivered.
Begin to confess your deliverance,
confess your healing.
If it is true for you, you are healed!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
If the word of God is true for your life, say, "I am healed; I am delivered!"
Say, "Thank You Jesus!"
I can't hear you!
[Thank You, Jesus!]
Say, "Thank You Jesus!"
Mean it!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Juliet Bwalya 07/06/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 12/06/2018